http://www.flexbar.com/pages/privacy-policy

HomeAboutReplica Proofing & Inspection Reprorubber PuttyReprorubber Casting MaterialPuttyThin PourMedium BodyCartridgesAccessoriesAllFacsimile Quick Setting CompoundKitsRelease AgentPowderLiquidAccessoriesAllMachinable WaxBlockCylinderAllFine Proofing & Fixturing AlloysFixturing AlloyFine Proofing AlloyAllVideo & Optical Inspection Video Inspection & Measurement SystemsOptiflex QCZ-2000 Series "Granite Z"Optiflex 3000 SeriesUltraflex 5000 Series "Granite Z"Video & Optical InspectionLight Source & Fiberoptic LightingPocket Optical ComparatorsAccessories, Light Sources, & CamerasLight Sources & IlluminatorsSystem AccessoriesCameras & Camera AccessoriesMicroscopesInspection Stereo MicroscopesInspecto-MikeHi-Res Hand Held Video Measuring MicroscopeAdvanced Function Toolmaker's Microscope SystemsBorescopes & Video Borescope Inspection Video Borescope Systems & AccessoriesFlexible Fiberoptic BorescopesWireless Borescope SystemsRigid Optical Lens BorescopesInspection & Measurement Dimensional MeasurementCalipersDigital & Dial Indicators & AccessoriesDial Test Indicators & HoldersMicrometers & AccessoriesTriga-Bore™Universal Comparator Gage SystemAllGages & Setting RingsBore Gages & Settings RingsChamfer & Countersink GagesDigital Depth Gages & MicrometersElectronic Thickness GagesGroove Gages, Internal & ExternalHeight GagesRock-It Spherical Diameter Plug GagesSnap GagesSteel Ring Cylindrical Ring GagesSplit Ball Type Probe Measuring SystemAllHardness Testers & AccessoriesTest Blocks & IndentorsDurometersBench Top Hardness TesterPortable Hardness TestersHardness Testing FilesAllMetrology Standards & AccessoriesCalibration MastersInspection Balls & SetsHole Location PlugsThread Gages & AccessoriesCalibration LabelsAllSurface Roughness Testers and Comparator PlatesFlexbars & Gage Stands Comparator Stand, Granite & Steel BasesHeavy Duty Granite BaseSteel BasesAllSwiss Style Indicator ArmsStrato Line 3D Articulated Gaging ArmsClassic Line 3D Articulated Gaging ArmsAccessoriesAllFlexbar Universal Holder Positioning ArmsOriginal Flexbars"In-Line" Fine Adjustor Holders/PositionersFlexbars on Weighted & Vacuum BasesJumbo Flexbars®Float 'N LockFlexbar Vise-GripOff-The-Post Flexbars®Long Reach Jumbo Flexbar ClampFlexbar Tom ThumbAccessoriesAllIndicator Stands & Magnetic BasesMagnetic Base StandsIndicator StandsMagnetic BasesAnyform Base StandsSwivel ClampsAllOriginal Flexbar®Machine Tool AccessoriesMachine Safety Systems LatheSlide-Track Latheguard™Latheguard™Flexbar E.I.M.B.™Lathe Chuck Safety WrenchesFlexbar ChuckguardsFlexbar Helical Lead Screw CoversTravelguard™AllMilling MachineUniversal Mount Mill & Grinder GuardTotalguard™Visorguard Universal3-Axis Universal Mount Interlocked Guards7" Bridgeport Drawbar GuardFlexbar VisorguardLong Reach Visorguard™AllDrill PressFlexbar VisorguardLong Reach Visorguard™Visorguard UniversalDrill Press Visorguard Kit3-Axis Universal Mount Interlocked GuardsDrill/Chuck VisorguardFlexbar Drillguard™Universal Pole Mount Adapter KitAllGrinder, Sander, & SawPivot Mount Grinder Guard and Universal ShieldFlexbar Grinder Guard Deluxe™Scroll Saw Visorguard KitBand Saw Visorguard™Disc Sander GuardSpindle Sander GuardsBelt Sander GuardsTop Cover GuardLower Motor GuardAllSafety Shields, Machine Controls, & PerimeterPanelguard™Flexbar Sensing-Saf-Start®The Lexan® Flex-Shield™Chipguard™ DeflectorsEyeguardThe Lexan® Versa-ShieldFlexiguardThe Flexbar Viseguard™Motor ControlsAll
Menu
Cancel
View cart
Home
About
Replica Proofing & Inspection
Reprorubber Casting Material
Putty
Latheguard™
Flexbar E.I.M.B.
Lathe Chuck Safety Wrenches
Chuckguards
Travelguard™
All
Milling Machine
Universal Mount Mill & Grinder Guards
Totalguard™
Visorguard Universal
Latheguard™
Flexbar E.I.M.B.
Lathe Chuck Safety Wrenches
Chuckguards
Travelguard™
All
Milling Machine
Universal Mount Mill & Grinder Guards
Totalguard™
Visorguard Universal
All
Privacy Policy At Flexbar Machine Corporation, we recognize the importance of privacy to visitors of our web site. This privacy policy explains what type of information is collected when you visit our web site and how that information may be used. Our web server automatically creates log files for each visitor who accesses our site. These “access logs” allow us to make our site more useful to our visitors. The access logs do NOT record a visitor’s name, address, phone number, credit card numbers, or any other personally-identifying information. Rather, they contain some or all of the following information:
The IP address of the machine which accessed our web site.
The date of the visit.
The time of the visit.
The pages visited on our website.
The browser being used.
A list of files downloaded or viewed.
Any errors encountered.
Certain web pages on our site may use “cookies” which are small amounts of information stored by your web browser software on your workstation. In most cases, this information is temporary in nature (called session cookies) and is deleted as soon as you leave the web site. The use of cookies is solely for the purpose of allowing the user to interact with the website in an effective manner and is not used to collect personal information in any way. Flexbar does collect personally-identifying information (such as your name, e-mail address, address, telephone number and/or credit card information) from our website only if you choose to provide that information to us. Such information may be collected as part of an event registration, request for more information, or product purchase. This information is only used for our internal purposes or to inform users of upcoming events and special announcements.
Flexbar does not disclose, give, sell, or transfer any personal information about our website visitors unless required for law enforcement or otherwise required by law.
Occasionally, Flexbar’s website may contain links to other websites. Flexbar is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those sites. We encourage our visitor to be aware of this when they click on any such links and urge them to review the privacy statements of each website visited.
Flexbar reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Any changes to this policy will be posted to this page as soon as reasonably possible, so please check this page periodically. Use of Flexbar’s website constitutes consent to any policy then in effect. If you have any questions or comments concerning our privacy policy, please contact us sales@flexbar.com or by mail at:
Flexbar Machine Corporation
250 Gibbs Road
Islandia, NY 11749
Contact
Contact
Tradeshows
Dealer Locator
Application Solver
Copyright © 2020 Flexbar Machine Corporation.
Empire Theme by Pixel Union. Powered by Shopify
Added to your cart:
Subtotal
